Wrapped up today,
uh with five more picks. Um
and um you know, first I want to thank
the uh everybody in the organization for
the past few days here.
Uh it's really more than 3 days. I mean,
this it's an entire year. Uh especially
with our scouts, all the time that they
put in
on the road, away from their families.
Um
you know, they are really the lifeblood
here um scouting these players and um
you know, all the people in the
building, our our department, uh the
personnel department, uh the coaches
that put so much time and energy into um
into evaluating these guys and
communication I thought was was really
good uh between
between the personnel department and the
coaching. Um
and then just our entire support staff,
our medical, um you know, when we bring
these guys in on 30 visits, it's uh
there's a lot of different touch points
with everybody in the building. Um you
know, strength coaches, trainers,
um our dieticians, um
um Ev sits down with them, too.
Um he'll give us his evaluation. So, um
there's there's so much time that's put
into it for these 3 days, but uh I
really appreciate all the work that uh
that they've given us here. Um
so. Mike, uh
day three picks a lot of times don't
come in immediately and contribute on
offense or defense, but do special
teams, but given that you have you want
to create competition on the offensive
line, how quickly do you feel like Kube
and Carmona can get in that mix and have
a chance to start? Yeah, I mean, listen,
these guys have played a lot of
football, both of them. Um
and um they they really do fit the
definition of always say like the tough,
smart, dependable. I mean, they are they
epitomize it. Those two guys. Um and
they've um like I said, they've had a
lot of snaps there in college football.
Um and um they're physically, you know,
where they're at right now, the size.
Um I think they can come right in here
and and and compete. How much do you
think that experience
>> [clears throat]
>> maybe not necessarily make up for what
what they may lack athletically, but
benefit them as far as, you know,
getting them in here and getting ready
to compete right away? Yeah, I think
there's a maturation to it, especially
with the old lineman. Um that uh you
know, they've played so much and um and
you know, they've
they've been around, you know, probably
a lot of different coaches. Um you know,
both guys had um
you know, uh Fernando was um at uh San
Jose State, went to Arkansas.
And then with Pat, was at Notre Dame and
then finished his uh his season for your
national champs. Um
and um
yeah, so they they played a lot of
football, so I think that does help,
Buck. Can you give a a cliff notes
version, maybe on the on your five
today, just their strengths, what
they're about? Yeah, I mean, I'll hit uh
Fernando first. I mean, that like I just
said, the the the intangibles part with
these guys. Um
you know, they're gritty. Um you know,
we have these these alpha tags
uh for leadership for for these
offensive lineman. And and um both him
and Pat both have that. Um and Fernando
played left tackle um you know, at uh
San Jose State, played some tackle in
'24 at Arkansas and then played guard
and then also has the capability of
playing center, too. Just really hadn't
done it much in a game. They've done it
in practice before.
Um with Pat, you know, Pat has obviously
played center at Indiana uh this past
year. Um I've never seen a guy get an
MVP um as an offensive lineman in the
Rose Bowl.
Uh it just speaks to, you know, the type
of player he was uh there for them, uh
the leadership. And Pat's also played
some guard at um
at Notre Dame as well.
How about your other guys? Um Yeah, so
with Nick, I mean, Nick was a highly
productive uh running back at Penn
State, played played played a lot of
snaps there, too. He was a
basically started there 4 years.
Um it's funny, I remember turning on the
film, I forget who I was watching at
Penn State a couple years ago, it might
have been two, three years ago, and I
see this number 10 and he runs really
angry and he's fast and he can catch the
ball and we had a there was a guy we had
in Kansas City, Pacheco, kind of
reminded me of him a little bit.
Um so I've I've been feel like I've been
watching him for a long time. Um
and then with with Jaren,
you know, he was really interesting
because um you talk about an athlete. I
mean, the guy was a a linebacker for 3
years and then he didn't play tight end,
you know, and then picked it up and
uh he's you know, he's played H-back,
he's moved around, he's kind of played
fullback a little bit. Um you know,
really athletic, really good special
teams player. Um so he's going to
I think contribute there right away on
teams. You had Jackie, too. Yeah, and
Jackie I'm sorry, Jackie, too. Yeah,
Jackie um
you know, the the first time you saw
him, I kind of watched a little bit of
him at Baylor last year. Um you know,
he's playing five technique, he's
playing three technique, so I think he's
versatile. Um
he's explosive on contact, he's twitchy.
Um and you know, we see him here, he can
probably play a little big end, but
mostly, you know, inside as a DT for us.
Um coach Aaron Weinkauf actually had him
at the East-West um when he coached in
that game.
Um and our scouts got to visit with them
there. Um and then Aaron actually was at
his pro day and worked him out, too. So,
we've had a lot of different touch
points with him. Staying with the
offensive lineman, you talked as far
back at least as the at the owners
meetings to us about being able to
sacrifice some some traits and get that
toughness and and and play with that.
What do you lose when you don't have,
you know, the prime athleticism
there and how does a line
maybe function fine
without that? You know, sometimes with
these guys, but that's a good question
because, you know, the toughness part
always shows up. That's the intangibles
part. They're usually strong, they're
tough, they're smart. Um and sometimes
they're so smart, sometimes they know
some of their limitations as well. Uh
they're so technically sound. Um so, you
know, um when you have some of these
guys playing next to each other, they're
kind of the same way. Um they they make
up sometimes for, you know, whatever
limitations they might have um you know,
with their toughness and and their
technique and fundamentals. If you're
slotting Jackson right now, you have him
at center or guard?
Um right now, obviously with the new
staff, he's he's playing both. He's
going back and forth between guard and
center. Um you know, he's played
probably more guard primarily right now,
but uh but he also has some center snaps
and and those guys will be
interchangeable here throughout OTAs and
training camp, too. With uh with
Singleton, first off, what did the eval
tell you about the injury? How quick do
you think he can be back? And then two,
does he add something to the running
back room, a trait that maybe you guys
didn't have that you were kind of
looking to fill?
Um you know, I think he's a he's a
bigger back. Um he's probably a little
bit you know, he's a little bigger than
Tony. Um and um you know, the speed, he
actually catches the ball really well
out of the backfield, too.
Um and as far as the injury, uh he's um
you know, he should he should be you
know, I don't put a timetable, but you
know, when he comes in here, we'll tell
you, look, but you know, he's he'll be
participating here in the spring. Are
you going to cut some people now in
order to have a bigger undrafted class?
You're not going to keep yourself to
four guys here, are you?
Yeah, those are the things we're working
on here throughout the week. Um you
know, tonight and and really throughout
the week.
Um cuz technically, all these guys, I
know you might hear some stuff on
Twitter and all that stuff and um none
of these guys can really be
signed until they they walk in the
building. Do you expect to have a
regular-sized class opening?
Um we'll see how it shakes out. Yeah.
What's the schedule for these guys? When
how soon will they be back here?
Uh they'll be back today, Sunday,
uh what, the end of the week? Yeah.
Yeah.
Mike, with with this draft, do you feel
that uh you kind of
you know, a lot of talk about best
player available at spots, but you have
holes on this roster. Do you feel that
you may have taken a good step with this
class to try try and fill those spots?
I do. I mean, I think that's the the
goal. I mean, obviously you want to take
the best player, but you try to marry up
um value with need. Um there's there's a
part of that.
Um without reaching for the need. And
that's why I always say like just take
the best player. Let's not just reach
for a guy just cuz we need, but but I do
think we we we did um we did fill some
needs. Yeah.
Anything else? This is
Mike, does the does the UDFA like how
you how you target the UDFAs? Does that
kind of fill in the holes that maybe you
feel like you missed or is it are those
guys that kind of just add value to the
current draft class? Yeah, I I think
it's an extension of really the draft
class, you know, but
we I wish we could have 20 picks
sometimes, but
No, you didn't.
I know.
What do you got, Paul? Um I know you did
a lot of work at at defensive back in
free agency and everything. This is just
the third time in the history of the
franchise in Nashville that the draft
hasn't included defensive back. What's
it say about where you are with Marcus
Harris and Tony Adams? And I know the
early indications are it's maybe a focus
for you with undrafted.
Um yeah, I mean, obviously we we added
um you know, Flott and Alontae, too. Um
you know, to come in here and start. So,
um
and then having Marcus back and signed
Tony, as well. So,
um well, it like even when the draft is
over, it doesn't, you know, we're still
working here on trying to improve the
roster. It's never going to stop,
whether it's
waiver claims, tryouts, um you know, it
it doesn't stop. So, um we're going to
continue with every position to to to
keep working, try to get the best 53 by
start of the season. You you talked
about [snorts] coach Mack, I guess at
your pre-draft press conference. What
was it like to see maybe
everybody in that war room wearing the
coach Mack shirts today and then the
people across the league kind of
honoring him as well?
Yeah, you know, I thought it was it was
it was it was a great tribute uh to him
and how many people he um
he really had an impact on the league.
Um and
you know, the more you find out uh
I mean, he knew everybody throughout the
week, it seems like. Um so, I thought it
was really special to see um
you know, to see us wear these shirts
here today and um
and and some of the pins that you know,
everybody was wearing throughout the
draft. It was a
a great tribute to him.
All right.
Thank you, everyone.
>> Okay, appreciate it.